overnight you have the Benchmark nifty50
that's trading very close to the high
point of the day right now up about half
a perc or thereabouts and moving edging
closer towards that 22,300 Mark the
broader Market's in fact looking even
more sanguin if anything and you have
the midcap index that's up about 8/10 of
a per or thereabouts and you have the
small cap 250 index that's up over a
perent right now so understandably the
market breath tilted in favor of the
advances in terms of the ke contributors
on the nifty50 let's take a look at that
list you have bti AEL at the top
followed by Lassen and tuo and Tata
consultancy Services infosis up and
about before the presentation of its Q4
results on the other end of the spectrum
you have the biggest loser in the form
of nestle India and some reports
emerging over the course of the last
couple of days that the company is in
fact using an added sugar in its uh
cerilac which is widely consumed and
this is something that is uh only in
developed nations in a few developed
Nations India included in Europe and in
the UK there is no added sugar there is
some pressure on the stock and account
of that we will talk about that in just
a bit but for now let's turn to ICI
Lombard SMY right good morning Al ICI
Lombard is the focus for today the stock
is up about 3 and a half% and uh to
break down numbers for us we have my
colleague Punit joining in pun tell us
about the performance of IC Lombard yeah
thanks so the company had issued a
steady gross domatic premium income
growth uh in this quarter compared to
last year while the combined ratio have
also seen a reduction for the better now
for the quarter 4 the gdpi income grew
at 22% coming at at roughly 6,070 cror
versus
4,900 uh in this time last year while
the combined ratio has improved to
roughly % from 104% previously the
solvency ratio has also done well coming
in at just 2.6 times uh 2.6 times versus
roughly 2.5 times previously while the
Pat has grown at roughly 177% compared
to previous year coming in at 520 crores
now when you go to the product mix we've
seen uh a stable uh for each of the
products like motor they are at 19%
versus 20% previously uh two key data
points here within the products they
said that the uh within Motors the Third
party rate hike has not been announced
for 2025 which augers well for the
demand for the particular product while
with in the health and travel verticle
they've said that the retail health
agency grew roughly 22% compared to
previous year where it competes with the
LI of star Health in this segment uh
we've seen roughly fire as well as the
other segments maintaining market share
roughly as well as uh the product
Revenue coming at at stable 14 to 15%
which is the St now finally what are the
brokerages saying HSBC has uh raised has
has maintained a Target price of roughly
uh 1,990 rupees which is a 20% upside
from the current levels they say that
the uh The Firm has increased its market
share gains and is focused in each of
these segments going forward as well
lowering the loss ratio given forward
they say that uh they they see that
meeting fi25 operating ratio guidance
should lead to even higher EPS goal from
the current levels while it says the
firm is firmly placed to deliver a f a
premium growth compared with the
industry so IC L doing very well on the
results and the stock is up roughly 3
and a half% today back to you all right
thank you so much Punit for that uh and
on that note let me introduce you to the
guest for today we have llau Duna CIO
value X wealth connect and sawati hka
Senior Equity technical analyst uh
research at Nal Bank Securities welcome
to both of you and thanks for taking the
time out I'll come to you uh Mr Duna
first on the focus which is IC Lombard
with see uh results are pretty much in
line with what was expected you're
seeing brokerages giving a Target price
of an upside of 18 to 20% are you also
seeing that sort of gains uh in the
longer
term uh yes I I am looking at you know
seeing that kind of improvement in
financial performance Drive the pricing
uh up as well because if you look at you
know from a macro situation as the
economy continues to grow General
Insurance uh will also Al grow at 15 to
18% perom and since icsi Lombard has
been consistently maintaining its market
share in most of the important segments
like fire motor uh Etc which are the
profitable segments we will continue to
see growth coming into this sector and
as well as growth for icsa Lombard even
the management has indicated that there
could be a 15 to 177% growth in the
premiums and with the loss ratios
looking better I think this uh stock
should do much much better over the
longer
term okay fair enough you know we we had
initially thought of taking Nestle but
then when we discussed it the stock was
not reacting too much and then after
that of course let's pull up the chart
and see where it's currently trading
it's it's down as much as 3 and a half
to 3.7% off the low point of the day
lart I I I do want to uh broach the
topic with you because reports emerging
that there is as much as 9% of added
sugar
in uh cerilac in India and certain other
markets now it's hard to quantify the
impact of this but I can't see parents
very comfortable with the idea of sugar
in uh in SE in in the food that they're
giving their children we we were trying
to look at the revenue contribution and
it's not very clear the breakup between
uh you know baby food in the context of
the overall milk product space but do
you think that there could be a sizable
impact and how would you react to this
if you are an
investor so if you actually analyze the
business of nestle a large part of the
business comes from the Maggie noodles
and the ketchup part of the thing part
of their business a significant portion
of Revenue also comes in from their milk
product space and CAC has been one of
their main stay products as far as the
baby food is concerned now uh while this
news report you know or the reports
suggest that uh these are these are some
inadequacies we also need to understand
that this stock always has been priced
at a huge premium over other fmcg stocks
and we could see that with this kind of
news the premium can get uh shaved off a
bit uh as far as you know unless we
start to be see some regulatory action
coming in you know saying that okay
Nestle is now not allowed to sell this
or some action is being taken by uh you
know Regulators in the space that could
have us higher significant let's say
negative impact as long as that doesn't
happen I think on a sales basis you may
not see too much of an impact because
you know in reality um people who are
this kind of news really doesn't impact
uh sales directly because a lot of
people believe that okay the product of
the company is good and you know they
would go by the brand that it's a global
brand they will give us good products
Etc but any regulatory action in terms
of asking them to stop production or
sales in this could could mean a
significant downfall from these levels
as well all right uh so regulatory
action is what we're going to watch out
for in this uh specific counter because
uh that's the key key uh factor that may
avoid the stock here but let's start
with the queries now the first one is
from himanta and this one is on IC
credential they say they bought the
shares at a price of 619 rupees STI this
is a short-term question so I'm going to
come to you on this one uh
it's it's slightly higher than what the
current price is what do you do you have
a target for the shorter term in this
particular
counter yes as of the view is definitely
a positive stock is fing in the pattern
of the high formation Al the interesting
fact as of it is well placed about the
shortterm moving average that is 20day
moving average which is also positive
indication but
we okay we we unfortunately just while
STI was is giving out her advice on that
particular stock have lost her feed
we'll get her back shortly in the in the
meanwhile let me take the next question
we'll we'll revisit ICC appr but the
next question is from moit and he's
writing in from Luda he's asking about
idfc First Bank which he has bought at
levels of
26.94 and those are attractive levels if
you actually think about it because the
stock is currently trading above the 80
rupe Mark okay so I'm told we have
swatti Swati back Swati you were talking
about IC Pro what's the advice
here yes Alex the overall view on this
particular company is really positive
because I I was explaining on the
technical front that the stock ising in
the pattern of
high also the interesting fact that it
is welled about the shortterm moving
aage D and as we have seen a very good
amount of a rally from almost 500 to 640
levels within a very short span of time
say within a span for two months so
profit booking cannot be denied at the
higher levels I will suggest to hold on
counter as long as it's maintains 600
support levels uh once it manages to
give the breakout of breakdown of 600
levels and only we can witness some sort
of a profit booking so those who are
having any long positions they can hold
on upside and looking for immediate
Target of 640 then 660 levels on the
high side but keep your long positions
by maintaining a stop loss of 600 okay
uh we've got a couple of questions and I
had already uh taking the first one but
I will repeat it moit from Lana is
asking about idfc first which he's
bought at levels of 26.94 attractive
levels his Horizon is about 2 years and
we've got Shri Kishore Sharma from miari
in Bihar who's bought at level of 61.6
to and his uh time frame is as much as
uh 3 years uh he's wondering both of
these individuals wondering what the
prospects are llot what do you make of
it it's currently trading above the 80
Mark what's the potential for upside
from here so I think the potential
remains strong Alex because you know uh
this bank has been focusing on the
retail liability side as well as retail
asset side and uh you know its strength
has been in that space and we've seen
them you know expand a lot in the retail
liability Side by opening more branches
collecting deposits so they've seen a
fairly good uh deposit growth NPS have
been fairly low so given that you know
this space is continuously growing you
are going to see uh significant growth
uh opportunities for the bank and that
should result in much much higher
valuation so I would say that if one is
willing to hold on to this stock for the
next two years to two to three years you
would get uh above average Returns on
this uh
counter all right uh next counter we're
talking about is uh pamal Enterprises
now this question is coming in from
Rajesh uh they say they want to know the
fundamental view on this particular
stock uh and uh Mr Duna we saw the stock
getting affected by the aif rules that
came out a couple of months ago but
we've seen recovery from that but
fundamentally how do you see the stock
in the longer term so I think over a
longer period of time yes the stock
should uh you know give investors good
returns but they've made a large amount
of investment in um you know in the
Pharma space and in spaces which are
which will be impacted with these aif
rules if at the moment I believe RBI is
also looking at this uh the rules in a
little bit more sympathetic manner but
probably over period of time these rules
will get uh tightened and they will have
some impact so from a long-term
perspective yes there could be growth uh
opportunities but you know there are
also various other uh opportunities in
the space which could give you fairly
you know good returns and one can look
at those as well where you know you're
seeing more um clarity on the
upside Point Ori and cement is the next
counter that we're focusing in on and
namita has got this question she's
specifically looking for a 3 to 6 month
view and a technical view at that STI
what's the view on the charts my view on
this particular counter is little bit
cautious Alex because why I'm seeing
that from the month of the January
itself we are witnessing a sell selling
pressure from almost 292 now the stock
is stading at almost 200 levels and more
downside can be SE into this particular
counter because we are witnessing a very
strong resistance at 220 225 levels as
long as doesn't give the breakout of the
same levels we are not likely to witness
a positive movement on the higher side
so I will suggest to book the profits or
to exit the long positions whenever we
get a rise towards to 222 225 levels uh
as of now 198 197 is acting as a crucial
support level if it's sprak that
previous swings slow more selling
pressure is likely to be intensified and
which might take a stock back to level
so be bit cautious try to exit positions
on every rise all right sorry next
question is on the counter yes Bank this
is uh from Anil they say this is a good
time to invest in the stock NOW the
stock hasn't been doing uh too much in
the last couple of days but has given
about
46% returns in the last one year do you
see uh some kind of an upside in the
shorter term on this
counter this counter has not performed
really very very well on the technical R
from almost Year from last four years
the stock was trading within this range
of 15 to 20 levels now it has came out
of that particular range but we are not
witnessing a very much price momentum in
this particular counter so those who
those who have extra capital and a
longer time Horizon in hand then only
one can invest in this particular stocks
because I believe Discounter is likely
to witness a very slow rally on the
higher side upside as of now the stock
May T towards 2 30 30 to 34 levels
whereas on downside it has a strong
support levels at around 20 so those are
interested for a slow momentum couns one
can invest but my personal opinion to
stay away from the S Bank rather than in
this particular counter one can go for
into the SBA Federal bank or the these
are the good banking stocks one can
invest all right uh yeah I mean
incidentally his time Horizon is as
money as two years but in any case I
think that view holds true we have to
slip into a very quick break we've got
more questions that we will take so do
stay tuned
[Music]
welcome back you're watching ask profit
and we're in the midst of taking all of
your questions the next one we're taking
is on
irfc uh which is a question coming from
arind who's writing in from Andra
Pradesh he's bought at levels of 148 the
stock is currently trading very close to
that Mark he's got a long-term view on
the stock so he's wondering whether to
keep holding or to sell at this juncture
llot what's view on this particular
stock so uh if you look at it from a
long-term perspective yes Railway
financing is is going to see significant
growth especially given the outlay that
has been envisaged uh you know over the
next five years government is looking at
putting in close to five lakh crores of
investment in this space and that should
uh you know encourage uh you know or see
the need for raway finance ing uh and
and hence the company should do better
but when you look at it uh you know
ultimately it is also financing only a
single sector so obviously Whenever
there is a little bit of a downturn or
you know things are not moving or
interest rates move higher you can see
some portion of negative impact so I
think given that the stock is already
trading at a significant premium to its
long-term uh you know Price to Book
values I think the upside from here will
take take a little longer period before
you start seeing uh significant returns
going forward and so one should look at
other Alternatives rather than staying
with uh this company for the long term
all right next counter we're talking
about is Engineers India this is uh from
Ravi from Hyderabad they bought the
stock at 160 a piece and it's currently
trading at 2115 soti we've seen the
stock zoom in the last 1 month itself do
you see more upside to this particular
counter should you maybe take some
profits off the table
the view is positive the stock in the
formation of the inverse head and
shoulder pattern as of now it is forming
the right shoulder of the inv should
pattern we have seen that the stock has
taken a very good support of 200 dma
sorry 200 levels and on on high side it
has a breakout of a neckline breakout
which comes right around 235 I believe
that this pattern is likely to be
continued and on the end of near future
it can give the breakout of 235 upside
we can see the target of at least 260 to
280 levels on the high side so for the
shter term duration I will suggest to
hold on as long as it's maintain the
support of 200 levels for imate Target
of 260 to 280 levels all right uh this
is a bit of a broad question but Lan
this one's for you we've got jitendra
goyel very young viewer tuning in 22
years old and he's got 50 lakhs that he
wants to invest uh into the equity
markets and he's clarified he said that
this is for the long term at least least
a few years but he's worried that in the
next few months there could be a
significant amount of volatility on
account of the central elections which
is just around the corner right now and
he's wondering in the event of a market
crash what should he do so should he
hold off till the dust settles to deploy
the funds what do you think and how
should he go about making that first few
Investments right thank you Alex I think
uh this is a question that you know most
investors are being faced with but uh I
think one should look at it a little bit
you know in a perspective that how much
do elections really affect markets over
a longer period of time if your outlook
for investment is like say 3 years four
years elections really haven't impacted
markets
dramatically uh to to reduce the
earnings growth that you're seeing you
know whichever government comes at the
end of the day everybody is pro growth
and pro economy and that's where you are
seeing U seeing the um positive side of
it on the other hand the market has
already factored in that there is a
positive uh you know Trend that this
current government is going to continue
and that is factored into the market at
this point in time so if there's any
sign that you know that is unlikely to
happen then you will you might see a
knej reaction where there could be a
considerable selloff in that kind of uh
scenario because of the uncertainty
created out of the election results so
uh as an investment strategy I think
it's better to put in at least 40 to 50%
of your investment
upfront and or maybe even higher maybe
you can go up to 60 70% of your
investment upfront in good stocks which
have long-term Outlook and keep the
balance 30 to
40% for the uh any volatility that may
come out post election results because
it could be you know even depending on
who gets appointed as a finance minister
Etc you could see be some volatility in
certain counters and then you can take
advantage of that volatility and deploy
the balanc portion of that time right uh
very interesting point of view Alex uh
from what I'm hearing that election is
now a nonevent for the big investors but
definitely retail investors may get
affected more than that but uh the next
counter that we're talking about is
cachi Industries uh this one's from
sorab and uh they bought the stock at 48
rupees it's currently trading at 60 4
rupees a bit of a profit here here lands
slau and uh the time Horizon here is 3
to 4 years now considering uh the fact
that he's already sitting on a bit of a
profit do you uh do you uh suggest
holding on to the
stock yes RI I think that uh if you look
at the company the company is doing well
and its profits are growing sector in
which it is in is also growing and if
you look at the return ratios you know
return on Equity is good above 177% and
so given that the long-term Outlook is
positive one should remain invested
because in the short term you might look
at booking profit there's also potential
that you may miss out in the longer term
rally so I think one can stay invested
in cachi Industries even at these
levels VI on sigi uh it's unchanged as
things stand right now the next question
is coming from Sagar and uh he says he
points out that that he's currently uh
in uh the UAE he's asking about mazgan
docs and I'm actually curious about this
as well he's bought 100 shares at a
purchase price of
205 um and he's asking whether he should
book profits at this juncture the stock
is currently at 21 98.65%
to
do yeah yes definitely the stock has
given a very spectacular rally in the
2023 almost the whole year was the good
year for this particular counter as of
now the counter is stading near by 2200
levels the overall setup is still
positive on the technical front downside
it has a very good support of 2100
levels if person needs the cash then he
can book at least partial profits at the
current market price or else they can
hold the long positions as long as this
particular cter holds the 2020 is the
very crucial support level for discount
if it's break that level then the
short-term Trend will turn into on the
negative side so I will suggest to Hold
On by keeping a profit stop loss of 2020
and upside I believe if it's manages to
give a breakout of 2250 upside door gets
opens for 2400 level so it's a whole bit
of my end by maining keep profit STS uh
coming back to you STI on this one
because it's time sensitive hant is
asking this question he's gone shot on
ABB uh and at
6340 intraday what should his strategy
be oh on the intraday basis he has um
took a short positions but this counter
has shown us ruls from 20 days moving
average from almost he has shorted at a
day low I will suggest to exit the short
positions because the pullback rally is
likely to be continued towards at least
uh upside 6590 and above that levels we
can witness 6650 levels also so I will
suggest to else maintain the strict stop
loss of 6550 for short positions and any
coming uh dis particular any DS comes
towards at Le
6450 he can exit the long positions the
overall trend looks positive and we are
witnessing a full back rally on the Inay
basis so I would suggest to exit on
every deeps all right uh unfortunately
now we're completely out of time on the
stion of ask profit thank you so much
STI and Mr Duna for joining us and for
answering so many questions for us and
viewers uh thanks for tuning in on uh
ask profit uh and if you were not able
to take your questions today we'll
definitely try and take them tomorrow
but don't go anywhere we have lots more
lined up for you on NV profit
[Music]
[Applause]
e e
[Music]